Howard Leung | Web Developer

I'm a self-taught, selt-motivated coder with a passion for technology, a desire for continuous improvement, and proficiency in the web development fundamentals. With each project, I strive to write code that is clean, maintainable, and delivers a positive user experience.

Skillset

HTML, CSS, and Javascript (ES6)

Conversion of mockups into code

Development of a basic full-stack CRUD application (MEAN stack)

Implementation of external libraries and API's

JQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, NodeJS, NPM, and Git

Basic understanding of object-oriented programming concepts

MVC architecture

Asynchronous Javascript

Mobile-friendly layouts

Education

University of Hawaii at Manoa - Graduated: May 2014 BBA Entrepreneurship Shidler College of Business

Work Experience

Hawaii Army National Guard - January 2010 to January 2016
Military Police

Participated in field-training exercises.

Held accountability for equipment and soldiers in my team.

Teamwork

Arancino Di Mare - January 2013 to February 2016

Waiter/Busser

Provided customers with table service by answering questions, taking food and drink orders.

Communicated effectively with managers and kitchen staff.

Performed multitasking in a fast-paced environment.

Longhi's - January 2012 to December 2013

Busser

Assisted servers with providing guests with table service.